seasteading.org 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy - The Seasteading Institute | The Seasteading Institute

Privacy Policy 

**The Seasteading Institute respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of The Seasteading Institute.

**Credit card details**

Any financial information you provide to us will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of The Seasteading Institute.

**External Sites**

The Seasteading Institute is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows The Seasteading Institute to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and The Seasteading Institute does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to The Seasteading Institute and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through The Seasteading Institute have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email the [webmaster](mailto:webmaster@seasteading.org).

Posted on July 30, 2012 at 3:16 pm 

Categories:   

### Written by
